(Penny:)Thanks for clearing that up.
(Sheldon:)Regardless, coronary problems
are eminently treatable.
(Sheldon:)What's more likely going
to kill Howard's mother
(Penny:)are the
antibiotic-resistant
(Sheldon:)super-bugs festering
in every nook and cranny
(Sheldon:)of this hospital.
(Penny:)Okay, you're not helping.
(Sheldon:)Disagree.
(Leonard:)Go sit over there.
(Sheldon:)I'll sit over there--
it looks cleaner.
(Leonard:)Is there a history of
heart disease in your family?
(Howard:)My family is the history
of heart disease.
(Howard:)There's a cave painting
in France
(Howard:)of one of my ancestors
doing this:
(Bernadette:)So it's probably genetic.
(Howard:)Well, maybe.
(Howard:)Mom also had just gotten some
news that might have upset her.
(Sheldon:)What?
(Howard:)It's not important.
(Bernadette:)Come on, Howard,
I'm going to be your wife.
(Bernadette:)You can share
anything with me.
(Howard:)You'd think that.
But no.